(

poojauidesigner@gmail.com



poojauidesigner.com



linkedin.com/in/pooja-jh



New York, Metropolitan area



I am a UI designer with a background in pastry art, human development, fashion, and interior design. I was born and raised in India and I have always been passionate about design and creativity. I am experienced in communicating with customers and dedicated to understanding what clients want and need. I empathize with clients and take pride in my organizational skills and attention to detail.

PROJECTS:

 Wagtales- A location based app created using Balsamiq, Sketch and Invision for pet parents to find anything petrelated from pet clinics to dog parks or emergency facilities in any area.

POOJA JHUNJHUNWALA

UI DESIGNER

- Grocers- An online shopping app designed using Sketch where users can shop their groceries from stores in their area with contact-free delivery.
- Plated Pixiedust- A recipe app created using Sketch, Usability hub and Invision in which users get a step by step recipe and video for vegetarian and vegan recipes.
- Ping- A messaging app mini project created using Sketch and Flinto.
- Remember- A note taking app mini project created using Sketch.

EXPERIENCE

The Global Vegetarian- Recipe Developer and Blogger

2019 to now / Website: <u>www.theglobalvegetarian.com/</u> Platforms: @theglobalvegetarian

- Design website using Squarespace and develop recipes for blog.
- Write and create content- food and lifestyle blog posts, including editing pictures and videos for each recipe.
- Share content on social media platforms such a Instagram, Youtube, Pinterest and TikTok and analyze data pertaining to posts to create content based on engagement.
- Partner with brands by using their products and giving shareable useful feedback to community and create shareable content.

Cake by Pooja- Founder and Head Baker

2016 to 2019 / Kolkata, India

Onset Retail store- Intern and Event Managing

SKILLS & TOOLS

Sketch Invision Balsamia Flinto Keynote iMovie **User Flows** Competitor Analysis Wire framing Prototyping **Usability Testing** Style Guides Color schemes Iconography Typography Branding Responsive Design` HTML

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

2020 - 2021

UI Design Program- An intensive project based course completing many UI/UX projects Specialization: Front end Development including Javascript, CSS and HTML.

Institute of Culinary Education,NYC 2015-2016

Pastry and Baking Diploma Cake Decoration Diploma

JD Birla Institute, Kolkata 2012-2015

Bsc in Home Science-Human development, Design and Food science

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi, Bengali